# Joiner David Cantillo Camargo

# Full stack engineer

joinercantillo0813@gmail.com | +573003771370 | Linkedin | Github | Portfolio Barranquilla, Colombia

## **PROFILE**

Experienced blockchain developer with a strong track record in creating secure smart contracts for Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain, Polygon, and Solana. I have experience in DeFi and DEX environments. Also served as a smart contract auditor for a Metaverse gaming project-sandbox, ensuring security and compliance

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Senior Smart Contract Auditor**

07/2022 - 07/2023

#### Sandbox 🛮

- Enhance the AR system by integrating GPT-4 model to enhance the content and avatar generation system
- Developed and audited smart contracts designed to manage item auctions and transactions, enabling the seamless exchange of in-game assets.
- Preserved security and integrity for ASSETS on the blockchain while still allowing the speed and flexibility that players and creators demand by leveraging benefits of ERC-1155 standard
- Ensure the everlasting scarcity and verifiable scarcity of non-fungible items with the ERC-1155 token standard
- Design a staking pool to provide incentives to token holders who are actively locking their funds in smart contracts

# Full Stack Blockchain Developer

11/2020 - 06/2022

#### Maxos LLC ☑

- Launched 3+ blockchain wallets such as Blade, Modden and Hashpack of chrome extension and desktop application
- Achieved building open-sourced 4 DeFi platform on HECO chain that offers fast transaction time and low cost
- Completed 3 decentralized social media web applications based on Lens protocol for integrating Ethereum
- Leveraged AWS ECS proficiently to oversee and scale hundreds of containers, prioritizing scalability and efficient container administration.
- Facilitated in launching Ocean Protocol which allows 100+ businesses and individuals to monetize data based on AI and blockchain
- Established a global DAO known as a "savings protocol" to manage pooling deposits and mitigate financial panics for 7 companies
- Implemented cutting-edge security measures to 100% ensure the safety and integrity of all transactions
- Enhanced application performance by Angular 6 component-based development in view of future Angular framework transitions

#### Full Stack Developer

04/2019 - 09/2020

#### Neoteric 🗷

- Orchestrated and mentored a team of 3 developers to expertly craft and deploy 3+ cutting-edge websites, resulting in an impressive 30% increase in customer engagement
- Migrated an application developed in Angular 4.0 to Angular 5.0

- Maintained and refactored existing websites (refactoring slow implementations, merging 40 projects into 1 generic project)
- Collaborated with the product and dev teams to improve the efficiency of the platform by 25%
- Orchestrated the creation of a robust staging environment for rigorous testing and developed a domain management system utilizing AWS Route 53.
- Contributed to product development and upgrading of the current site to boost customer satisfaction by 17%.
- Conducted unit and load testing for high profile customer-facing applications, which reduced system failure rate by 70%

### Full Stack Developer

05/2017 - 02/2019

#### Lama AI 🛮

- Accomplished 20+ front-end and back-end applications utilizing React.js, Node.js, and Typescript
- Used various Angular 2 custom directives and developed reusable components and templates that can be re-used at various places in the application
- Created Typescript reusable components and services to consume REST API's using component-based architecture provided by Angular 2
- Designed and maintained 30+ REST APIs, such as data retrieval services with OpenAPI specifications
- Collaborated with 3 engineering and design teams to integrate external APIs into web pages and applications
- Wrote 200+ unit tests to ensure 100% of code within SDLC was without bugs
- Constructed 50+ customized reusable components by harnessing the power of React, Redux, Material UI, Bootstrap, and HTML/CSS
- Enhanced user interfaces by updating menus more intuitively to attract 5% more clients than the previous quarter

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Degree in Computer Science Technological University of Bolivar

04/2012 - 03/2017 | Bolivar, Colombia

SKILLS		
• Typescript/JavaScript	• Solidity	• Python
• Node.js	• SQL, MongoDB	• React.js/Next.js/Gatsby.js
• Ethers.js, Web3.js	• Scikit-Learn	• TensorFlow
Agile/Scrume	• Vue.js	• Angluar.js
• RestAPI	• Docker	• AWS
• Git		

# LANGUAGES

English

Spanish